在我们开始我们的content provider代码之前，我们
Before we start coding our content provider, let's
要先确认manifest是正确建立的。
make sure the manifest is set up correctly.
你需要更新包含应用标签的androidmanifest.xml文件夹
You need to update the androidmanifest.xml file within
再添加到contentprovider里去。
the application tag to add the content provider. So
这样安卓的内容解析器才能访问它。
that android's content resolver can see it. The
当归档到content provider类的包名确定时，
authority really should match your package name. While
authority也应匹配包的名字。
the name indicates which file your content provider
接着，开始写on create函数。
class is in. Next, let's code up on create.
我们要给database helper创建一个实际变量。
We'll begin by creating an instance variable for our
在on create里面，我们初始化实际变量。
database helper. In on create, we initiate our instance variable.
我们通过返回true值来告诉安卓
We return true, which is how we tell Android that
content provider已经创建成功。这结果显示
the content provider has been created successfully. It turns out
我们可以通过重复同一个之前对数据库做过的测试
that we can repurpose the same test we did
来测试新的content provider。这
for the database to test our new content provider. This
让你能够测试你的content provider 代码
will allow you to both test your content provider code
验证content provider calls是怎样代替SQLI
and see how the content provider calls replace the SQLI
数据调用的。通过使用Android
database calls. Let's start by using Android
studio复制testDB来测试provider。
Studio to copy TestDB to test provider.
我们重命名测试创建DB,来测试删除DB。
Let's rename test create DB, to test delete DB.
所以开始启用一个干净的记录。我们只需要留下一个M背景点在那里删除
So we can start with a clean slate. We'll just leave the M context dot delete
数据库行。其他测试也是
database line in there. We'll leave the other
同样，很快就可以达到目的。
test the same, we'll get to it soon.